[{"answer": " Alex, good to see you. I havent seen you in a long time. What have you been u", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 16, "question": "", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": " Hey, great to see you too. Ive been studying a lot and getting ready for m", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 18, "question": " Alex, good to see you. I havent seen you in a long time. What have you been u", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Thats right.  Youre in the nursing program. Hows that going", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Hey, great to see you too. Ive been studying a lot and getting ready for m", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Pretty good.  The textbook part was pretty brutal, but I enjoy being with th", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Thats right.  Youre in the nursing program. Hows that going", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Are there a lot of guys in your program", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Pretty good.  The textbook part was pretty brutal, but I enjoy being with th", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " No.  Actually, I think Im one of four.  There are about 250 students in the progra", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 31, "question": " Are there a lot of guys in your program", "qSentId": 30},{"answer": " I guess nursing has traditionally been a field that attracted mostly women", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 37, "question": " No.  Actually, I think Im one of four.  There are about 250 students in the progra", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Yeah, it is.  But, its starting to change nowadays.  More and more men ar", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 38, "question": " I guess nursing has traditionally been a field that attracted mostly women", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Do your guy friends give you a hard time for being in the nursing program", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 42, "question": " Yeah, it is.  But, its starting to change nowadays.  More and more men ar", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " They did a little at first.  But now that they see what a great career Ill have", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Do your guy friends give you a hard time for being in the nursing program", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " Its pretty cool that men and women are choosing jobs now that they might no", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 47, "question": " They did a little at first.  But now that they see what a great career Ill have", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Yeah.  I see women now that have jobs that were usually a mans job in the past", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Its pretty cool that men and women are choosing jobs now that they might no", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": "Thats interesting.  Ive seen men doing jobs that were traditionally womens job", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 55, "question": " Yeah.  I see women now that have jobs that were usually a mans job in the past", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Right, its true.  My brother is a stay-at-home dad because his wife is a lawyer", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 59, "question": "Thats interesting.  Ive seen men doing jobs that were traditionally womens job", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " You dont hear a lot about dads staying home with the children.  Its usually th", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 63, "question": " Right, its true.  My brother is a stay-at-home dad because his wife is a lawyer", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " Yeah, but like you said, roles are changing for men and women more and more", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 67, "question": " You dont hear a lot about dads staying home with the children.  Its usually th", "qSentId": 66},{"answer": " Well, look at me even.  I had a job interview at a local fire department for ", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 68, "question": " Yeah, but like you said, roles are changing for men and women more and more", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": "Oh, yeah.  I forgot.  How do you feel you did on the interview", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 72, "question": " Well, look at me even.  I had a job interview at a local fire department for ", "qSentId": 71},{"answer": " I think I did pretty well.  I feel like I could do as good a job as any man tha", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 73, "question": "Oh, yeah.  I forgot.  How do you feel you did on the interview", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Im sure you could.  Youve been studying so much, so I bet you answered all th", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 77, "question": " I think I did pretty well.  I feel like I could do as good a job as any man tha", "qSentId": 76},{"answer": " Yeah.  I could answer everything they asked me.  They said I was the onl", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 81, "question": " Im sure you could.  Youve been studying so much, so I bet you answered all th", "qSentId": 80},{"answer": " Thats awesome.  I hope you get the job", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Yeah.  I could answer everything they asked me.  They said I was the onl", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Thanks.  Me too", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 89, "question": " Thats awesome.  I hope you get the job", "qSentId": 88},{"answer": " Well, it seems like were both going into careers that are not too typical for ou", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 90, "question": " Thanks.  Me too", "qSentId": 89},{"answer": " Times are changing", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 94, "question": " Well, it seems like were both going into careers that are not too typical for ou", "qSentId": 93},{"answer": " Thats true", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 95, "question": " Times are changing", "qSentId": 94},{"answer": " Well, I guess Id better get going.  Good luck with all of your patients and on th", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 96, "question": " Thats true", "qSentId": 95},{"answer": " Thanks.  Good luck with the job too.  Call me and let know what happens", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 100, "question": " Well, I guess Id better get going.  Good luck with all of your patients and on th", "qSentId": 99},{"answer": " I will.  See ya", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 101, "question": " Thanks.  Good luck with the job too.  Call me and let know what happens", "qSentId": 100},{"answer": " Bye", "docId": "07-01", "aSentId": 102, "question": " I will.  See ya", "qSentId": 101}]
